<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Berlin App</string>
    <string name="berlin">Berlin</string>

    <!--CATEGORIES - TITLES-->
    <string name="cool_places_title">Cool Places</string>
    <string name="museums_title">Museums</string>
    <string name="bars_title">Bars</string>
    <string name="clubs_title">Clubs</string>
    <string name="food_spots_title">Food</string>

    <!--COOL PLACES RECOMMENDATIONS - TITLES-->
    <string name="kreuzberg_title">Kreuzberg</string>
    <string name="raw_temple_title">RAW Temple</string>
    <string name="hackesche_hofe_title">Hackesche Hofe</string>
    <string name="prenzlauer_berg_title">Prenzlauer Berg</string>
    <string name="mauerpark_title">Mauerpark</string>

    <!--MUSEUMS RECOMMENDATIONS - TITLES-->
    <string name="hamburger_bahnhof_title">Hamburger Bahnhof</string>
    <string name="puppentheater_museum_title">Puppentheater Museum</string>
    <string name="juedisches_museum_berlin_title">Jüdisches Museum Berlin</string>
    <string name="east_side_gallery_title">East Side Gallery</string>
    <string name="neues_museum_title">Neues Museum</string>

    <!--BARS RECOMMENDATIONS - TITLES-->
    <string name="barbie_deinhoffs_title">Barbie Deinhoff\'s</string>
    <string name="geist_im_glas_title">Geist im Glas</string>
    <string name="ae_title">Ä</string>
    <string name="dschungel_bar_title">Dschungel Bar</string>
    <string name="klunkerkranich_title">Klunkerkranich</string>

    <!--CLUBS RECOMMENDATIONS - TITLES-->
    <string name="about_blank_title">://about blank</string>
    <string name="tresor_title">Tresor</string>
    <string name="kitkat_title">Kitkat</string>
    <string name="berghain_title">Berghain</string>
    <string name="club_der_visionaere_title">Club der Visionaere</string>

    <!--FOOD SPOTS RECOMMENDATIONS - TITLES-->
    <string name="burgermeister_title">Burgermeister</string>
    <string name="moksa_kitchen_title">Moksa Kitchen</string>
    <string name="standard_serious_pizza_title">Standard Serious Pizza</string>
    <string name="konnopkes_title">Konnopke\'s</string>
    <string name="fine_bagels_title">Fine Bagels</string>

    <!--COOL PLACES RECOMMENDATIONS - CONTENT-->
    <string name="kreuzberg_content">
        The most alternative districts of all and one of the best known
        neighbourhoods of Berlin. It\'s easy to distinguish the moment when you
        step into Kreuzberg as suddenly all you see around are quirky shops,
        small restaurants, cosy cafes and funky looking people.\n\n
        On top of that there\'s an overwhelming number of the amazing street art
        on every step, including some of the most famous Berlin pieces.
        There\'re lots of nightclubs, pubs, cafes,
        little shops and small restaurants – surely Kreuzberg is a place to be!
    </string>

    <string name="raw_temple_content">
        Located close to Warschauer Strasse S-Bahn and U-Bahn station,
        this former railway maintenance yard now serves as an alternative culture
        center. Railway tracks are still on the ground, some of the old buildings
        still stand – this industrial scenery is a perfect setting for
        a place like this.
        \n\nRAW Temple is where numerous community
        projects take place. From art exhibitions and rock concerts to
        open-air cinema or workshops for young and adults – everything can
        be found there! On Sunday the place turns into a big flea market.
        Sadly rumors say shopping center is going to be built
        in this location so make sure to visit before capitalism destroys
        this raw and cultural playground!
    </string>

    <string name="hackesche_hofe_content">
        Most people go to Hackesche Hofe to admire the
        beautiful art-deco building (it is indeed spectacular).
        But not many know that the next entrance leads to the courtyard
        that is a paradise for every street art lover. The place
        is literally covered in various forms of street art – graffiti,
        posters, murals, stickers, you name it! Located not
        far away from Alexanderplatz, Hackesche Hofe is highly recommended!
    </string>

    <string name="prenzlauer_berg_content">
        Former East Berlin area that always has been in
        the opposition, now is one of the most desired
        places to live in the capital of Germany.
        And you can\'t blame all these people dreaming of being residents
        of Prenzlauer Berg. Packed with cozy cafes and small
        boutiques and full of beautiful architecture it surely must be
        a wonderful place to live in.
        \n\nPrenzlauer Berg makes a perfect
        alternative to the famous landmarks of the city. After the busy
        sightseeing day it\'s worth stopping in that district for a cup of coffee,
        just to enjoy the easy-going lifestyle Berlin is so famous for.
    </string>

    <string name="mauerpark_content">
        At the edge of Prenzlauer Berg, where te Berlin Wall
        and its Death Strip used to be, the most hip of city\'s parks can
        be found. It\'s especially worth to visit Mauerpark on
        Sunday as that\'s when the whole magic happens – one of
        the biggest flea market, public karaoke singing or, when
        the weather is nice, a massive barbecue!
        It seems like only cool, trendy and young Berliners
        visit the park to chill out with friends and so it\'s
        worth visiting the place just for people watching!
    </string>

    <!--MUSEUMS RECOMMENDATIONS - CONTENT-->
    <string name="hamburger_bahnhof_content">
        Berlin\'s foremost contemporary art museum,
        Hamburger Bahnhof is the name on the tip of everyone\'s tongue.
        A rich collection of works from Beuys, Twombly, and Warhol is
        complemented by travelling exhibitions and temporary showcases
        of cutting-edge talent and household names.\n\n

        The space itself is not to be missed: the museum
        takes its name from the former Berlin–Hamburg rail station,
        and the echoes of grandeur can still be heard
        in the airy halls under high ceilings.
    </string>

    <string name="puppentheater_museum_content">
        Equal parts creepy and cute, the Puppentheater
        Museum in Neukölln is home to more than 300 puppets and marionettes.\n\n

        Their cheerful and cherubic faces are the thing of
        nightmares for some, but others might be interested in the
        dolls\' personal histories and cultural heritage.
        For those who dare, readings are scheduled
        regularly for both children and adults.
    </string>

    <string name="juedisches_museum_berlin_content">
        Dive deep into the history of Jewish
        people at the world-famous Jewish Museum.
        It\'s a vibrant celebration of Jewish history and
        culture housed in a dazzling building designed by Daniel Libeskind.\n\n

        You could easily spend a few hours
        here: the exhibitions are extensively
        researched and thoughtfully presented.
        Fully untangling stories of the migration,
        diversity and persecution of Jews in Germany may take
        some time but is well worth the effort.
    </string>

    <string name="east_side_gallery_content">
        What was once the Berlin Wall is now a 1.3km
        gallery remembering the city divided. Located
        just off Warschauer Strasse on the border of Friedrichshain
        and Kreuzberg, the East Side Gallery is flush with tourists looking
        to experience the size and stature of the wall that split the city in two.\n\n

        The most iconic murals remain on the walls,
        so grab a beer and take a walk through Berlin\'s
        turbulent recent history – it\'s a popular spot for a
        summertime beer on the riverbanks, so you won’t be alone.
    </string>

    <string name="neues_museum_content">
        It\'s hard to argue with the impressive collection
        of ancient artefacts housed at Berlin\'s Neues Museum.
        The building itself is a work of art:
        extensive damage incurred during the Second World
        War left the structure crumbling, but an in-depth
        architectural revival led to the museum reopening in 2009 to much acclaim.\n\n

        The Neues Museum hosts
        several immediately recognisable pieces.
        The standout? Don\'t miss the original bust of Nefertiti.
    </string>

    <!--BARS RECOMMENDATIONS - CONTENT-->
    <string name="barbie_deinhoffs_content">
        A quintessentially "Berlin" watering hole,
        drenched in pink neon light and walls emblazoned with
        years of graffiti. Frequented by the city\'s most colourful
        characters – the beers are cheap, the atmosphere fun, and it\'s LGBT friendly.
        \n\nThe aesthetic is pitched somewhere between John Waters hyper-kitsch
        and retro-futurism with its gaudy pink walls and shabby furnishings.
        It\'s a mixed LGBT crowd, with statuesque drag queens rubbing shoulders
        with butch, tattooed girls. Tuesdays is an all-night happy
        hour for drinkers on a budget.
    </string>

    <string name="geist_im_glas_content">
        A really beautiful bar with great
        attention to detail in everything they do. The
        staff are smiley, the decor is gorgeous and they
        serve the best cocktails in Berlin that won\'t blow your
        backpacker\'s budget. The best bit? These kind
        souls will even help you cure your hangover the
        next day with MEGA brunches and legendary pancakes.
    </string>

    <string name="ae_content">
        This bar, simply called "Ä", is
        on one of Berlin\'s best nightlife streets.
        Weserstrasse (in Neukölln) leads from Hermannplatz
        to the south, and along the road are a scattering of new bars,
        small clubs, and trendy cafes. The bar Ä offers nights of live
        music, events, and meetups. The social bar is casual and has two
        large rooms (one smoking, one non-smoking) which provide a great
        atmosphere for a relaxed but fun night out. Occasional DJs and a
        kicker table are just the cherry on top.
    </string>

    <string name="dschungel_bar_content">
        Unless you\'re a German speaker, you
        would not expect much from the unassuming
        entrance to Dschungel Bar aka "Jungle Bar".
        But once inside, you\'ll be transported to the wilderness
        at the heart of Neukölln. With an abundance of greenery and actual
        real-life frogs, this is definitely one of the weirdest bars in Berlin.
    </string>

    <string name="klunkerkranich_content">
        Located on top of a multi-story car park,
        Klunkerkranich is the best roof-top bar in Berlin by a mile.
        This is where the city\'s beautiful young things hang out on
        hot summer days, but don\'t worry, there\'s nothing pretentious
        about this saucy spot.
        \n\nThe bar and urban gardening project has a
        strong community vibe, and the very reasonable 3
        euros entry fee goes towards keeping it green and
        providing excellent live music for lazy Sunday afternoons.
        If you\'re looking for the best place to watch the sunset in
        Berlin, you\'ve just found it.
    </string>


    <!--CLUBS RECOMMENDATIONS - CONTENT-->
    <string name="about_blank_content">
        ://about blank (no this is not a typo!) is a
        formerly illegal, multi-room club by Ostkreuz
        S-Bahnhof in Friedrichshain. Despite the glitzy disco ball,
        about blank is anything but glamorous!
        \n\nIt\'s a short walk from Salon Zur Wilde Renate, and like that club,
        it\'s a lightly renovated, re-purposed building with
        seemingly endless nooks and crannies to explore.
        There are two main dance floors inside, and in the
        summer DJs play out in the garden (which is open in the
        winter too, with a cosy bonfire).
    </string>

    <string name="tresor_content">
        The new incarnation of an old techno institution,
        Tresor Club is set in an abandoned power plant spanning
        22,000m² on Köpenicker Strasse in Berlin\'s
        Mitte neighbourhood. It\'s a labyrinth of concrete passages
        mazing into basement vaults and industrial halls.
        \n\nJust when you think you\'ve discovered all of Tresor\'s secrets,
        you realise you haven\'t! Inside, there are three separate but
        connected floors: Globus and +4Bar for house and
        experimental electronic music, and, of course, the famed
        vault which, reached through a 30m long tunnel,
        uncompromisingly presents the Tresor sound.
    </string>

    <string name="kitkat_content">
        Nights at KitKatClub are always somewhat
        erotic and subversive - this is Berlin, after all,
        and club nights aren\'t the sparkly-mini-dress-and-Top-40
        affairs they are in many other cities.
        \n\nAlthough this is technically a sex club, it\'s not the sleazy affair
        newcomers might expect. If you just want to dance to the
        famous techno and house beats, that\'s totally fine - it will
        feel like you\'re with a ton of friends and everyone just happens
        to be in sexy underwear. Off the dance floor, it\'s up to
        guests to participate as much - or as little - as they
        want in any other activities; consent here is
        strictly emphasized, and there\'s no pressure.
    </string>

    <string name="berghain_content">
        Sitting in a dusty lot on the border of
        Kreuzberg and Friedrichshain, Berghain is widely
        considered one of the best clubs in Berlin, if not the world!
        \n\nIt has three main dance floors: Berghain, a dark main room where
        most DJs play techno, and Panorama Bar, an upstairs space that\'s
        more focused on house. Then there\'s Säule, a new experimental floor.
        There\'s also a men\'s-only club on the first level called Lab.Oratory,
        and a smaller space known for live performances with a
        separate entrance called Kantine am Berghain. Let the
        good times Berghain!
    </string>

    <string name="club_der_visionaere_content">
        Club der Visionaere is a rustic and
        understated spot between Kreuzberg and
        Treptower Park. It sits on a canal in a small
        brick building and could be considered more of a bar or
        after-hours venue than a nightclub. Entry is
        usually five euro or sometimes free. The dance
        floor holds just 50 people, with most attendees spending
        their time hanging out on the wooden deck outside and
        enjoying the views of the river.
    </string>

    <!--FOOD SPOTS RECOMMENDATIONS - CONTENT-->
    <string name="burgermeister_content">
        There are plenty of great burgers found in
        Berlin, but none are quite as iconic as Burgermeister\'s.
        This joint first opened in a former public toilet outside the
        Schlesisches Tor U-Bahn station and, as a testament to
        its success, has now expanded to three locations.
        The menu is refreshingly simple, the cheesy fries as
        comforting as comfort food gets, and the mouth-watering
        vegan burger nothing like your token veggie option.
    </string>

    <string name="moksa_kitchen_content">
        Moksa is not one of those Indian
        restaurants exclusively serving traditional Indian food.
        Situated in Neukölln, this hip spot offers tempting fast
        food dishes including the guest\'s favorite – tandoori
        chicken tikka. If you\'re trying to find the best South Asian
        cookery in the city, reflecting both authenticity and creativity,
        Moksa surely won\'t let you down. This place is almost a Berlin institution!
    </string>

    <string name="standard_serious_pizza_content">
        Neapolitan-style pizza restaurants in Berlin
        aren\'t rare, but we\'re not complaining.
        Berlin\'s pizza renaissance has upped the quality of the pies
        by huge margins, and Standard in Prenzlauer Berg is a crowd-pleasing
        favourite. You can\'t go wrong with the Margherita, with its fior di
        latte mozzarella and San Marzano tomatoes, or the more out-there house
        white pizza featuring smoked cheese, semi-dried tomatoes,
        aubergine and olive pesto.
    </string>

    <string name="konnopkes_content">
        This venerable sausage stand has
        been under the same family management since 1930.
        After coming up with a secret recipe for ketchup
        (which was not available after the Wall was built),
        it was the first place to offer currywurst in
        East Berlin and still serves the most famous – and
        quite possibly the best – version in the city. Expect queues.
    </string>

    <string name="fine_bagels_content">
        Germany isn\'t exactly known for
        its bagels, but this Friedrichshain bagel
        shop-cum-café-cum-bookstore does a fantastic
        job bringing NY-style bagels and Jewish-American
        bakery sweets to Berlin.
        \n\nIt\'s hard to go wrong with anything on the menu here, and the espresso by Bonanza
        Coffee is the perfect complement. Settle in for an hour
        or two if the weather\'s bad, or pick up some forgotten
        holiday reading material at the Shakespeare and Sons bookstore.
    </string>
</resources>